[
    {
        "question": "Which country is Paris its capital?",
        "answer": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Washington, D.C. its capital?",
        "answer": "United States"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is London its capital?",
        "answer": "United Kingdom"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Berlin its capital?",
        "answer": "Germany"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Ottawa its capital?",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Rome its capital?",
        "answer": "Italy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Madrid its capital?",
        "answer": "Spain"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Canberra its capital?",
        "answer": "Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Moscow its capital?",
        "answer": "Russia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Beijing its capital?",
        "answer": "China"
    }
]